Taeko Harada

Software Developer

Calgary, AB. taecooo512@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/taeko-harada/

GitHub: https://github.com/TaekoHarada/ | Portfolio: https://portfolio2-ebon-pi.vercel.app/

SUMMARY

Currently enrolled in SAIT's Software Development program in Calgary, Canada.

Previously worked in Japan as a system administrator, web designer, and Flash creator.

Recently, I have been focusing on mobile development using Kotlin and web development with React and TypeScript.

SKILLS

Kotlin • JavaScript • TypeScript • Python • Java • C# • HTML5 • CSS

Frameworks: Jetpack compose • React • Next.js • Bootstrap • Tailwind • .NET MAUI

EXPERIENCE

Student Tutor (in Japan)

Apr 2011 - Dec 2011

Teaching Mathematics for junior high school students.

Information Technology System Administrator (in Japan)

Feb 2009 - Feb 2011

System administrator at the Information Technology Department of Kawasaki Heavy Industries, Ltd.

Achievements:

- > **Troubleshooting and Collaboration:** Connected users and developers, fixing issues and asking for fixing code. Collaborated to bridge gaps between technical and non-technical teams.
- > Efficient File-Deleting Script: Developed an efficient file-deleting script that reduced processing time by tenfold.
- > Oracle Database Table Spaces Expansion: Successfully coordinated the expansion of Oracle database table spaces, accommodating increased data volumes and ensuring system scalability.

_

Main roles:

- > Researching and solving system problems.
- > Improving systems by discussing with users, developers, and IT strategy department.
- > Configuration of Oracle database. (Expanding table spaces, defragmentation).
- > Export and import data (DB data, files).
- > Coding helper for Java, VB .Net developers.

Flash Creator (in Japan)

Oct 2007 - Jan 2009

Creating Flash contents by using ActionScript for mobile phones.

Web Designer (in Japan)

Apr 2007 - Sep 2007

Designing and coding websites with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP.

EDUCATION

Software Development

Sep 2023 - Dec 2024

Diploma (2-year)

the Southern Alberta Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Applied Mathematic

Bachelor of Science Osaka Women's University

Web Design

Part-time (6-month)
Digital Hollywood University

_